Islam Sabyr

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

) (+1) 737-235-9938

Sugar Land, TX 77498

Summary.

Proactive and personable job seeker currently pursuing a Bachelor's of Computer Science at North American University. Excellent written and verbal communication skills. An ambitious student with excellent research, time management, and problem-solving. Hard-working and organized in any type of task that is given to me, I believe my enthusiasm and specialized experience would make me an asset to your team

Work Experience _

ServiceNow IT Intern RSM US LLP

July 2022 - Present

Houston, Texas

- Worked to understand and collaborate with groups across IT to deliver solutions.
- Participated as a stakeholder and team member for the operation of the IT Solution platform, including but not limited to: project planning, development, deployment, support, maintenance, and testing.
- · Tracked, analyzed, and reported delivery metrics.
- Created Business rules, Client Scripts, UI Policies, UI Actions and Script Includes.
- Managed Data with Tables, Import Sets and Update Sets.
- · Defined and developed notifications and reports.

Computer Programming Tutor

August 2020 - December 2020

Stafford, Texas

- North American University
- Taught students struggling with Java, HTML & CSS.
 Incorporated technology into lessons from other subjects, expanding students' technical abilities with integrated approach.
- Reviewed computer science class material with students to support discovery of correct answers to problems.
- Tracked and analyzed student progress to provide relevant feedback to students.
- Organized schedules to effectively help students excel and maximize revenue with robust calendar of sessions.
- Instructed a wide range of in various areas of Computer Science.

Projects -

Android application for Café order

September 2020 - December 2020

- Development of mobile application for making online orders using Java and Android Studio
- Fully Automated software to make easy for users
- Involved in the full life cycle of the project including analysis design, development, debugging, testing and deployment
- Wrote clean, clear, efficient, well-tested, and maintainable code
- Perform bug fixes and improve overall application's performance

Website for Restaurant order and reservation

January 2021 - May 2021

- Implemented responsive interface using JavaScript and HTML5 and CSS3
- Ensured layout of content is accessible on all platforms and devices
- Developed a strong knowledge of web technologies
- Self-developed the front-end and back-end of a user-friendly web application
- Tested websites and performed user testing and troubleshooting prior to live deployment
- Assessed risks associated with developing new features

Technical Skill

• Java · Android · Javascript · HTML5 · CSS3 · MySQL · Web Development · Algorithm · Data Structure · PHP · ServiceNow

Education .

NAU (North American University)

Stafford,

TX.

USA

Overall GPA: -

3.75

B.S. IN SOFTWARE ENGINEERING AND COMPUTER SCIENCE (EXPECTED GRADUATION: DECEMBER 2022)